Batı GÖKOVALI

batigokovali@icloud.com

batigokovali.com

inkedin.com/in/batigokovali/

= +90 506 593 97 43

Full-Stack Web Developer

Energy systems engineering graduate, worked for 2 years in the defense industry, always been passionate about computer science and coding, I completed EPICODE's full-stack developer course. I am actively pursuing a full-stack developer role in the EU, aiming to refine my skills and make a meaningful contribution to a company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Roketsan Missiles, Inc.

Jan 2020 - Nov 2021

Process Engineer

Ankara, Turkey

• As part of the pyrotechnics operations team, I've designed processes for production, created production routes, increased production line efficiency, planned production, and decreased costs.

Erdemir, Inc.

Jun 2018 – Aug 2018

Intern Zonguldak, Turkey

• In this internship, I did energy and exergy calculations, gas turbine analysis and efficiency calculations, TOE (tonne(s) of oil equivalent) calculations, and daily electricity market analysis for electricity generation. With this experience, I also become familiar with corporate workflow.

EDUCATION

EPICODE

Nov 2022 – May 2023

101 2022 111

Full Stack Development

Remote

• With this boot camp, I've learned and become proficient in popular and up-to-date web technologies. In this program, we also had teamwork projects which allowed us to improve our social skills and teamwork mindset.

Yaşar University.

Jan 2015 – Jan 2019

Energy Systems Engineering

Izmir, Turkey

HARD SKILLS

HTML5 - CSS3	Redux	MongoDB & PostgreSQL	MS Office	ERP
JavaScript & TypeScript	Node.JS	Postman API & Documentation	DaVinci Resolve	PLM
MUI	Express	GIT	Reaper DAW	
React	Bootstrap	OAuth	AutoCAD	

SOFT SKILLS

English – C1 Turkish - Native

CERTIFICATES & TRAINING

AS9145 Advanced Product Quality Planning Training	Aug 2021
Statistical Process Control Training	Aug 2021
FMEA Training	June 2021
5S Training	Nov 2020
Kaizen Training	Oct 2020
Systems Engineering Basic Level Training	July 2020
Systems Engineering Awareness Level Training	July 2020

AWARDS

1 st Place, Teknofest Turkey Rocketry Competition (1500 m)	Jun 2019
2 nd Place, Teknofest Turkey Rocketry Competition (3000 m)	Jun 2018

VOLUNTEERING

SosyalBen Foundation Jan 2015 – Jan 2016